阿巴拉契亚山脉 美国
Jeez!
天啊
抢修服务车
黑暗侵袭 2
With the community still
公众还未摆脱
shaken from last year's Slater's Quarry tragedy,
斯莱特采石场悲剧的阴影
here in Boreham, it's fresh heartache.
在博勒姆这里 又发生了新的惨剧
As the search for the missing women
由于搜索失踪女孩的行动
moves into the end of its second day,
已进入了第二天的尾声
hope is fading for Senator Kaplan's niece,
卡普兰参议员的侄女朱诺 和她的五个伙伴
Juno, and her five friends.
生还的希望越发渺茫了
Just behind me I can see one of the cave rescue teams
就在我身后 能看到其中一支洞穴救援队
emerging from the caverns.
刚从洞里出来
-Good luck, guys. -Thanks.
- 好运 伙计们 - 谢谢
Chimney's pretty tight. You all be careful in there.
洞口很紧 你们都要小心点
Will do.
我们会注意的
Sir, any signs of the missing women?
先生 是否发现失踪女孩的踪迹呢
Do you think you'll find them alive?
你认为她们还活着吗
How does this compare to Slater's Quarry?
这次的情况比起斯莱特采石场事件如何
That's enough now. Move back.
够了 退后
Do you think you responded quickly enough this time?
你觉得这次反应时间够快吗
-Greg, leave it! -Greg!
- 格雷格 别理她 - 格雷格
We're back on in four hours.
我们四小时内回来
-Get some sleep. -You too, boss.
- 去睡一会儿 - 你也一样 老板
Hey, you want to share a sleeping bag?
能跟你合用一个睡袋吗
What's that cologne you're wearing?
你用的什么古龙水啊
Yeah, six hours of sweat and dirt
哦对 进洞六小时 浑身汗臭
and all other kinds of shit.
泥泞不堪
I think I'll pass.
我还是别猜了吧
Lynch? What's up?
林奇 怎么了
What?
什么
Where?
在哪里
Look, get a tracker dog out there.
听着 带条追踪犬过去
See if you can find where she came out.
找到她出来的洞口
Yeah, all right, and...
好的 还有…
Let's keep the lid on this.
这事先别声张
All right, I'm on my way to the hospital.
好的 我马上去医院
- Right, Doc, how is she? - She's resting.
- 医生 她怎么样了 - 她在休息
We had to sedate her.
我们得让她镇静
I've got five girls missing
还有五个女孩没找到
and you put the one person
你却让唯一一个
who knows where they are to sleep?
知道线索的人睡着了
She was hysterical.
她有点不正常
Besides, she has no memory of the last two days.
另外 这两天的事她都不记得了
Whatever happened to her, she's blanked it.
不管那时发生了什么 她都忘了
Injuries?
伤势怎么样
It's only some minor cuts and bruises.
只是些轻微的割伤和挫伤
But her clothes were completely stained in blood.
但她的衣服却沾满了血迹
- So it's not her blood? - No.
- 不是她的血吗 - 不是
But she's been in a fight, all right,
但她打斗过
because judging by her fingernails,
从她的指甲判断
she scratched some big chunks out of somebody.
她曾狠狠地抓挠过某人
Test her clothes, get the blood type.
化验她衣服上血迹的血型
Get the blood type of the other five girls.
和其他五个女孩做一下对比
All right, let's see what you can do.
好吧 看看你能发现点什么
Hello, Sarah.
你好 莎拉
I'm Jenna Rios from Hyde County Sheriff's Department.
我是海德县警局的珍娜·里奥斯
This is Sheriff Vaines.
这位是万尼斯警长
- How you feeling? - Where am I?
- 你感觉怎么样 - 我在哪儿
You're safe. You're at Hyde County hospital.
你现在很安全 这里是海德县医院
We've been searching for you and your friends.
我们一直在寻找你和你的同伴
Two days ago you all set off on a caving expedition
两天前 你们去洞穴探险
and you never came back.
但一直没回来
We've been following your Boreham Cavern flight plan
我们根据你们的博勒姆洞穴探险计划搜寻
but we found nothing.
但什么也没找到
Can you tell us what happened to you?
能告诉我们 你们遇到了什么事吗
I don't know.
我也不知道
I can't remember anything.
什么都记不起来了
Sarah, your friends are still missing.
莎拉 你的同伴们还没找到
We need you to help us find them.
我们需要你的帮助
- Beth. - Beth.
- 贝丝 - 贝丝
What happened to Beth?
贝丝怎么了
What can you remember?
你能想起些什么
What about Juno?
记得朱诺吗
Jessie.
杰西
-Where's Jessie? -Your daughter?
- 杰西在哪里 - 你女儿吗
Sarah, Sarah,
莎拉 莎拉
I need you to listen to me carefully.
我要你认真听我说
Your daughter isn't here, Sarah.
你女儿不在这里 莎拉
She died.
她已经死了
- A year ago, in Scotland. - No.
- 一年前 在苏格兰 - 不
I know how hard this must be for you,
我知道这对你来说有多难接受
- but you have to try... - No, no. No! No.
- 但你必须尝试… - 不 那不是真的
Come on.
走吧
This looks like the end of the trail.
看起来痕迹到这里就没了
- What's that? - That there's Chapel Mine.
- 那是什么 - 那是小教堂煤矿
Cuffs, come here, come here.
卡夫斯 过来 过来
Go find them, boy.
去找到他们 小子
One of these days I'm gonna come up here
过几天我会过来
and help myself to some of this shit.
处理一下这些垃圾
What you found, boy? What you found?
找到什么了 小子 你找到什么了
Cuffs?
卡夫斯
Holy shit!
见鬼
-Sheriff. -Dan.
- 警长 - 丹
Keep it under your hat,
别声张
but we found one of the girls.
我们找到了其中一个女孩
Dog picked up her scent near the old Chapel Mine.
警犬追踪她的气味到了老教堂煤矿
- That's the other side of the county. - I know.
- 那在县城的另一边 - 我知道
Don't tell me we've been looking in the wrong place.
别告诉我 我们一直在瞎忙
Listen, I don't want to shift the whole goddamn circus.
听着 你不用把整个团队都带来
I just want a couple of volunteers to pick up
我只想要几个志愿者去搜索一下
where the dog left off.
警犬进去后就跑了
All right, give us an hour.
好吧 一小时后见
Cath, Greg, rise and shine.
凯丝 格雷格该起床了
Blood on Sarah Carter's clothes, A-positive.
莎拉·卡特衣服上的血迹 是A型阳性
Juno Kaplan is A-positive.
朱诺·卡普兰也是A型阳性
So? I'm A-positive.
那又怎样 我也是这个血型
Half the state is A-positive.
半个州的人都是
- Can she walk? - Sure.
- 她能走吗 - 可以
Wait, wait, you're not seriously gonna take her out...
等等 你们不会真要带她去…
Rios, get her dressed and get her in the car.
里奥斯 让她穿上衣服 带她上车
My granddaddy used to work down there.
我爷爷以前在那下面工作过
One time, him and two of his buddies
有一次 他和他的两个伙计
broke into a whole new cave system.
闯入了一个未知的洞穴系统
Really big.
非常大
Company bosses figured
公司老板们以为
there should be some rich pickings to be had,
那里资源应该很丰富
so they sent my granddaddy back down to
于是他们派我祖父
have a good look-see.
下去探查
He never come back.
他再也没回来过
Folks reckoned they must've broke clean through into hell.
人们猜想他们是闯入了地狱
The devil was mighty pissed.
惹怒了魔鬼
So you're telling me that
你是告诉我说
there's an uncharted cave system down there?
那下面有个未知的洞穴系统吗
Cool.
太酷了
There's a map of the mines here.
这有张矿井地图
If the caves are uncharted,
如果那洞穴没被探查过
we won't even know where to begin.
我们可能连入口都找不到
Bring the girl.
把那女孩带过来
Come on, Dan, she's the only one been down there.
行了 丹 只有她去过那里
All we gotta do is get a nod from her,
我们只需要她点点头
left or right. Narrows the search.
左边或右边 指示搜索的方向
There's a mountain full of caves and fuck-all time.
那山遍布着未知洞穴 我们没时间了
Could piggyback on the elevator cables.
那可以顺着那电梯电缆滑下去
You planning to go down there,
如果你们要下去
why not go down there in style?
干嘛不直接坐电梯呢
What, this old shit still works?
啥意思 这老东西还能用
Sonny, let me tell you,
小家伙 告诉你
this old shit-bucket will be working long time
这老东西肯定会比
after that MP3 of yours.
你的MP3的寿命长
Whatever.
随你怎么说吧
All right, Ed, get it going.
好吧 爱德 准备下去
I'm sorry, but Mommy's got to help people tonight.
我很抱歉 但妈妈今晚要帮助别人
Chica, when Grandma tells you to go to bed,
宝贝 奶奶叫你睡觉的时候
you go to bed, okay?
你要听话 好吗
Honey, I love you.
宝贝 我爱你
Okay, baby, I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
好的 宝贝 明天见
Rios, get yourself kitted and get her kitted.
里奥斯 你们两个装备好
We're going down.
我们要下去了
Okay, Sarah, I know this is difficult,
好吧 莎拉 我知道这很困难
but if you do this,
但如果你下去了
it could help jog your memory.
也许会有助于你恢复记忆
Your friends could still be alive.
你的同伴们可能还活着
You have to help us find them.
你得帮我们找到他们
Hey, Sarah, this might fit you.
莎拉 这件可能合适你
You want to lose that heavy metal.
你们别带枪下去
Gun blast down there'd be like dynamite.
在下面开枪就像是爆破
Come on, I'll put them in the car.
拿来吧 我一起放车里
My gun stays with me.
我在枪在
This is a missing persons case.
我们只是去找失踪的女孩
What the hell do you think you're gonna find down there?
你觉得下面能有什么事啊
Mummy.
妈妈
Right, let's get moving.
好吧 我们开始行动
Come on.
来吧
You all ready to ride?
你们准备好了吗
Yeah, let's do it.
没问题 开动吧
Jesus.
天啊
Hang on, just wait up a second.
慢点 等一下
Here, drink this.
来 喝口水
She's okay. Let me worry about her.
她没事 不用你操心
Come on, Dan, let's get to the goddamn cave.
来吧 丹 我们进去吧
Listen. Down here, I call the shots.
听着 在下面 我说了算
Is that understood?
明白吗
Loud and clear.
很明白
Let's go.
走吧
Should be a ladder down there.
那里应该有个梯子
How long have I been teaching you?
我教你多久了
Your light is your life.
你的灯光就是你的生命
All right. Okay, we've gotta go down another level.
好吧 我们再下一层
Greg.
格雷格
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
不是吧
Is it okay?
没问题吧
You know what's good?
想听听好消息吗
Modern mines have metal props.
现代矿井都是金属架构
Miners prefer these old wooden ones.
而矿工则喜欢老式的木质坑道
Why's that?
为什么呢
The metal ones don't give you any warning
金属架构矿井快垮塌的之时
when they're about to go.
不会给你任何警示
After yours.
你先走吗
Okay, we should hit the cave system somewhere up here.
那上面应该就是洞穴系统
Greg, go scout ahead.
格雷格 先上去探查
You got it.
收到
And Cath, you're next. Deputy.
凯丝 你下一个 副警长过来
I think I've found it.
我想我找到了
What the hell is that?
那是啥玩意儿啊
It's a pit pony.
是匹井下小马[旧时井下运输工具]
危险 请勿入内
Always a good sign.
总有好兆头
...Check it out. This is awesome.
…看啊 太不可思议了
Greg, T.L.
格雷格 热释光摄像机
Hey, hey. Don't... Don't touch anything.
别…别碰任何东西
This place is thousands of years old.
这地方有几千年历史
Well, you're hot.
你身材真好
Get away.
拿开
Sarah, do you recognize anything?
莎拉 你能想起什么吗
What?
怎么了
It's okay. It's okay, she just got spooked.
没事 没事 她只是被吓着了
Calcium deposits.
钙质沉积
Let's keep moving.
我们继续前进
It's okay, come on. Come on.
没事的 来吧 来吧
Come on, Sheriff, you can do it.
来吧 警长 你能行的
I ain't that old yet.
我还没那么老
Which way?
走哪条路
You recognize this?
你能认出这里吗
Cath, have a listen.
凯丝 测听一下
Anything?
听到什么吗
I don't know. I think I hear something.
我也不知道 好像有什么东西
Jesus!
天啊
- Oh, my God! - Shit!
- 上帝啊 - 见鬼
Fuck! Sarah. Look at me.
妈的 莎拉 看着我
She's moving.
她在动
No. There's no body heat. It's not possible.
不 没体温了 不可能
Deputy.
副警长
Sarah.
莎拉
She's been butchered.
她是被屠杀的
Six girls came down to this cave.
六个女孩到这洞里
One came out.
只有一个出去
Covered in her friends' blood.
浑身都是她同伴的血迹
Now, you tell me what the hell happened down here.
告诉我 这里到底发生了什么
Wait... wait a second.
等一下
You think she had something to do with this?
你认为是她干的吗
- This is fucked up! - Dan, get your team out of my face.
- 这可真操蛋 - 丹 叫你的队员让开
- Man, you brought her down... - Get off my back!
- 伙计 你带她下来… - 少啰嗦
Greg! Save it.
格雷格 别说了
I thought she was a victim here.
她不是这里的遇难者吗
What are you saying now, she's a suspect?
你现在是说 她是个嫌疑犯吗
I think she knows something.
我觉得她了解内情
I still got missing girls down here,
这里还有几个女孩下落不明
so let's keep our goddamn focus.
我们得集中注意力
I should never have let you bring her down here.
我真不该让你带她下来
I should never have let you...
我真不该…
Dan, I think she came through here.
丹 我想她是从这里出来的
All right, Greg, take point. Take point!
好吧 格雷格 你带路 带路
This is fucking bullshit.
这真他妈的太荒谬了
Deputy, look after her.
副警长 看好她
It's okay. Come on, you're gonna be...
没事了 走吧 你会…
Sarah, what is it?
莎拉 怎么了
I think there's something down here.
这下面有什么东西
We were attacked.
我们被攻击了
By what?
被什么攻击了
There's nothing down here
这下面没什么东西
that could have done this to a person.
能把一个人弄成这样
Sarah, what can you remember?
莎拉 你还记得什么
Sarah?
莎拉
We shouldn't stay here.
我们不该留在这里
You've got to try and think rationally.
你要尽量理性思考
You're scared.
你被吓坏了
Your mind's playing tricks on you.
所以产生了幻觉
I'm through.
我过来了
It's about a 50-foot crawl with some tight spots,
大概要爬五十英尺 有些地方有点窄
and then it opens out.
爬出来就宽敞了
All right, copy that.
好吧 收到
Sheriff, get your team together.
警长 集合队伍
Greg, we're coming through.
格雷格 我们现在就过来
Look out for them at the other end.
在出口接应他们
Okay, Rios, you go first.
里奥斯 你先走
I want you in front of her.
我要你在她前面
She's not getting out of my sight from now on.
现在开始 她不能离开我的视线范围
Come on, you're almost there. Come on.
过来 就快到了 再过来点
Hey! Whoa, come on.
小心
You need to breathe with me now.
和我一起做深呼吸
You need to breathe, okay?
你得深呼吸 好吗
Come on, keep it moving up there.
快爬 继续爬啊
Get a move on, you're slowing down.
快啊 你太慢了
Why have you stopped? Get a move on!
你怎么停了 快爬啊
How are you feeling? All right? Hey, hey, hey.
你还好吗 没事吧
Sarah... Sarah...
莎拉…莎拉…
Rios!
里奥斯
Sarah!
莎拉
For Christ's sake, Rios.
不是吧 里奥斯
Which way did she go? Which way?
她走的哪条路 哪条路
Shit!
见鬼
It's okay. It's okay.
没事了 没事了
That lady's a fucking psycho, Dan. Jesus.
丹 那女人就是他妈个神经病 上帝啊
- You okay? - I'm fine.
- 你还好吗 - 我没事
Look at me. How's it feel?
看着我 感觉怎么样
You want to kiss it better?
你吻一下更好
- He's fine. - Where's Vaines?
- 他没事 - 万尼斯去哪儿了
He took off after Sarah.
他去追莎拉了
Fuck! He doesn't even have a radio.
妈的 他没带对讲机
Five minutes in these honeycombs,
这些洞穴进去五分钟
they'll both be lost.
他们都会迷路
Okay, listen to me, listen to me.
大家听着 都听着
We've gotta catch up on them
趁他们还没走远
before they get too far ahead.
我们得赶上他们
This time, we stick together.
这次 我们一起行动
You understand? Okay, let's go.
明白吗 好吧 我们走
Yeah, come on.
走吧
Okay.
等等
Okay, there's falling rock here,
这里有落石
which, as you know,
如你们所知
means the roof's unstable,
这说明洞顶不稳固
so we have to tread carefully.
我们过去时得千万小心
Rios? You stick with me, okay? Let's go.
里奥斯 你跟紧我 我们走
Cath, can you hear me?
凯丝 能听到吗
Take it easy, that's gotta last.
别紧张 塌方结束了
Cath, come in.
凯丝 听到请回答
Cath, speak to me.
凯丝 说话
Dan, are you there?
丹 你在吗
I'm here, I'm here.
我在 我在
Are you hurt?
你受伤了吗
I'm stuck in a boulder choke.
我被卡在石缝里了
And I need something to support the rocks.
我需要有东西顶住这些石头
All right, all right. Don't you panic, don't you panic.
知道了 知道了 别慌 别慌
Listen to me. I'm gonna get you. Okay?
听着 我会救你出来的
We'll work at this end, all right?
我们会从洞口挖过来 好吗
You listen to me.
听着
You sit tight, we'll get to you.
你别动 我们会救你出来
Okay.
好的
Jesus. Come here, come on.
天哪 过来 快点
Come on, come on, come on. Jesus!
快啊 快啊 老天
Dan.
丹
Come on. Come on!
快啊 快啊
- Fuck! Fucking trigger-happy Americans. - Dan.
- 操 去你妈的乱开枪的美国佬 - 丹
Fucking only answer they've got to anything is a fucking gun!
就他妈知道乱开枪
Dan, don't let her hear you this way.
丹 别让她听见你这状态
There's a fucking ton of rubble between us.
这儿他妈有一堆石头阻隔着我们
She couldn't hear a fucking rock concert.
这边就算开他妈演唱会她都不会察觉
Dan.
丹
Okay.
好吧
Okay. Okay, Cath.
好吧 好吧 凯丝
Yes?
收到
We can't get through to you.
我们挖不通这石堆
Well, can't you drill it or det it?
就不能钻开它吗
You know we can't. It's too risky.
你知道不行的 太危险了
You're gonna have to work yourself free
你得自己想办法出来了
I can't, Dan, it'll crush me.
我没办法 丹 我乱动就会被压死
I need you here.
我需要你帮我
Okay,I'm gonna find another way around to you.
好吧 我去找找别的路
- Okay. - I'll get to you.
- 好 - 我会找到你的
I'm scared, Dan.
丹 我很害怕
That's good, yeah? Fear keeps you alert,
这很好 不是吗 恐惧会让你提高警惕
it keeps you alive, it's...
警惕能让你生存下去
I promise you,I won't stop till I get to you.
我保证 找不到你我决不放弃
I know.
我知道
Maybe I should stay with her.
也许我该留下来陪她
You know we can't help her here.
你知道待在这也无济于事
You hang in there, teammate.
坚持住 伙计
- No worries. - Okay, Cath.
- 别担心 - 好的 凯丝
Are you dry?
衣服没湿吧
- Yeah. - So you'll keep warm.
- 没有 - 那你能保持身体暖和了
You keep drinking.
随时补充水分
You stick with the drill, okay?
严格按照训练内容来做 好吗
Okay.
好的
We're gonna have to move off now.
我们现在得出发了
So you'll probably lose the signal.
信号可能会暂时中断
You stay positive.
别沮丧
- Okay. - Okay.
- 好的 - 好的
We're walking away. You stay on channel one.
我们动身了 你保持在一频道
Okay. I'll be on channel one.
好的 我会在一频道
You got your chance now.
你专心找路 把握好机会
Shit!
妈的
Fuck!
见鬼
What the fuck?
这他妈是什么
- Are these animal bones? - Jesus.
- 这些都是骨头吗 - 天哪
Dan! Dan!
丹 丹
Here we are, morning after the night before.
开始录啦 宿醉的我们
Here we go. Look at this face.
瞧瞧这张脸啊
Wake up, ladies.
醒醒吧 女士们
I feel like a pig.
我肯定像个猪头似的
- Now there's some water. - It's not nice.
- 这个看上去好多了 - 得了吧
- We all ready for this big, exciting day? - Yeah.
- 都准备好迎接这令人兴奋的一天了吧 - 没错
That's Juno.
这是朱诺
I'll believe that when I see it, all right?
我亲眼见到才会相信 好吧
How you doing?
感觉怎么样
- Yeah, I feel good. - Good.
- 感觉挺好 - 好
- Recording for... - For National Geographic.
- 此录像是为 - 是为国家地理录制的
For National Geographic.
为国家地理录制的
- Once again... - Recording our trip...
- 重来一次 - 此录像是为
To Boreham boredom Cavern.
我们到博雷汉姆荒废矿坑探险而录制
How do you think Sarah's doing?
你觉得莎拉状态怎么样
Do you think she's ready for this?
你觉得她准备好参加这次探险了吗
I mean, she just seemed a little bit...
我觉得她好像有些
You cut the camera?
你关相机了吗
- Sarah? - Put it away for, like, two minutes!
- 莎拉 - 把那玩意儿拿开 几分钟也行啊
- Where is that? - I don't know.
- 她们是在哪里 - 不知道
Holly! Could you take a break?
天哪 别拍了行吗
I just want to take a few more shots.
我只是想多记录下一点内容
This cave's a lot cooler than I thought.
这矿坑比我想象中的阴冷多了
- This wasn't in the book. - Good.
- 在书里可学不到这些 - 这下好了
Maybe that last jelly custard wasn't a really good idea.
早知道刚才就不吃那果冻布丁了
- How much further, do you think? - Thank you very much.
- 你觉得还有多深 - 谢了
- You sure? - Yeah, I'm sure.
- 当真 - 是的 没错
Okay, guys?
伙计们 都还好吧
Do you hear that?
你们听到什么声音了吗
Is that it?
就这些吗
Dead animals, hundreds of them.
动物的尸骨 成百上千的尸骨
-That's here. -This is not good, guys.
- 是我们现在待的地方 - 伙计们 不妙
-Can we get out of here? Which way? -That's this place.
- 咱们出去好吗 路在哪边 - 就是这里
-Come on. I don't know. -What do you mean you don't know?
- 快啊 我不知道 - 什么叫不知道啊
There's no breeze!
察觉不到风向
It could be any one of these tunnels! Take your pick!
每个路口都可能是出路 做决定吧
Fuck it!
见鬼
-Hello! -Please!
- 有人吗 - 别喊了
Is there anybody there?
有人吗 救命啊
Hello?
有人吗
What the fuck is that?
那东西是什么
Greg! Greg!
格雷格 格雷格
Greg! Greg, where are you?
格雷格 格雷格 你跑哪去了
Dan!
丹
Rios, you there?
里奥斯 是你吗
Dan, I'm here! Where are you?
丹 我在这呢 你在哪儿
Dan! Where are you?
丹 你到底在哪儿
Dan!
丹
Rios!
里奥斯
Rios! Where are you? Let me know where you are!
里奥斯 你在哪 告诉我你的方位
I can't hear you!
我听不见你
Sarah.
莎拉
You let him die.
你竟然眼睁睁看着他丧命
What the fuck was that thing?
那到底是什么鬼东西
Don't worry. It's just your mind playing tricks on you.
别害怕 你只是被自己的幻觉迷惑了
Dan? Greg?
丹 丹
Dan, is that you?
丹 是你吗
Can you hear me, Dan?
丹 你听得到我吗
Sarah.
莎拉
I...
我
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
我很抱歉没有信任你
They're blind. They track sound.
他们没有视觉 仅靠听觉追踪
You're louder.
你声音太大了
- Greg! Greg! - Cath!
- 格雷格 格雷格 - 凯丝
Where's everyone else?
其他人都哪去了
We got split up.
我们跑散了
- What the fuck are these things? - I don't know. I don't know.
- 这些怪物是什么 - 我不知道
- I want my fucking torch. - Shit. Sorry. Here.
- 快点亮荧光棒 - 妈的 抱歉 给
Is this okay? Okay? Okay. All right.
感觉好点了吗 别怕
Run. Run! Run!
跑 快跑 快跑
Jesus!
天哪
Dan!
丹
Jesus Christ, Dan.
老天啊 丹
Fuck. Fuck!
见鬼 见鬼
Are you there?
能收到吗
Can you hear me?
能听到我吗
Can you hear me? Is there anybody out there?
能听到我吗 有人在吗
Come in! Anybody?
请回话 有人吗
Up! Up!
向上 向上
Up!
向上
- Dan's dead. - Turn it off. Turn it off!
- 丹遇害了 - 关掉它 快关了
Come in. Anybody?
请回复 有人吗
Are you there? Can you hear me?
有人在吗 听得到我说话吗
Come on, can you pick this up? Can you hear me?
快啊 回话好吗 有人听到我说话吗
Dan? Dan, come in.
丹 丹 请回复
Dan, it's Cath. Come in.
丹 我是凯丝 请回复
- Dan's dead. - Dan. Come in, Dan.
- 丹遇害了 - 丹 请回复 丹
Vaines had his radio, Cath.
万尼斯拿了他的对讲机 凯丝
We don't know that. We... He wasn't clear.
还不能确定 他并没这么说
Dan? Dan, come in. Dan?
丹 请回复 丹
Give me that. Give me. Give me that.
把它给我 给我
I left him there.
我把他一人丟在那了
Those... Those fucking things attacked us and I left him there.
那些 那些怪物攻击了我们 我扔下他跑了
No. No, he promised he'd come back. He promised he'd come back.
不可能 他保证过会回来找我 他保证过
I heard him scream, Cath.
我听到他的惨叫了 凯丝
I heard him scream.
我听到他撕心裂肺的惨叫
He's gone, Cath, okay?
他已经死了 凯丝
No. No.
不可能 不可能
I ain't gonna run out on you.
我不会丢下你自己逃命的
You even try, and I'll kill you myself.
你要是敢跑 我会亲手了断你
We gotta move. Stay quiet. Come on.
我们得走了 保持安静 快
Jesus.
天哪
- Fuck. - Fuck.
- 见鬼 - 妈的
Fuck!
见鬼
- You'll have to jump. - It's too far.
- 你得跳过去 - 太远了
Use her to get across.
只能借助她到对面去
Go.
跳吧
- Fuck! - We have no choice.
- 见鬼 - 没别的办法了
Fuck! Fuck!
见鬼 妈的
Go!
快跳
All right, push forward!
好的 向前荡
Greg!
格雷格
Got washed out by the water last time.
上次在水里被搞得精疲力尽的
I... I can't go down there.
我 我不能下水
The water's flowing. There's a way through.
水在流动 一定有出路
No, no. Wait. Wait, please. Wait. Please. Wait!
别 等等 请等一下
Sarah. Sarah. Sarah! Sarah!
莎拉 莎拉 莎拉 莎拉
God.
天哪
No, no, no. Sarah!
不要啊 莎拉
- Come. Come. - All right.
- 跟上我 - 好的
- It stops here? - It's a dead-end.
- 水流到这里就止住了吗 - 是条死路
There's no way through?
没有任何出路吗
- No. - Fuck!
- 是的 - 见鬼
Fucking water.
该死的水
Hi, baby girl.
嗨 宝贝女儿
Hiya. It's Mommy.
亲爱的 是妈妈
I... I just wanted to let you know...
我 我只是想告诉你
That I love you.
我爱你
I want you to be good.
我希望你好好的
And kind.
要善良
And caring.
要有爱心
I want you to be a good person.
我希望你以后成为一个好人
You're so special, baby.
宝贝 你对我无比重要
Te quiero, te extra, baby.
我爱你 宝贝
My daughter's dead.
我女儿去世了
I know.
我知道
Everything you just said,
你刚刚说的那些话
you tell it to her face. We're not dead yet.
留着当面告诉她吧 咱们还没死呢
Come on. We'll keep moving.
走吧 我们不能停下来
Juno!
朱诺
Juno, I'm here to help you.
朱诺 我是来救你的
Get you out. You hear me?
救你出去 你听到了吗
I'm here with Sarah.
莎拉也跟我们一起来的
God.
天哪
What the fuck is this?
这是什么鬼东西
I don't know.
不知道
Now I wish I was back in the water.
我开始怀念刚刚泡在水里的时光了
What are these things?
那些怪物是什么
Death.
死神
Your friends, they're all dead?
你的伙伴们 他们都遇害了吗
Yeah.
是的
How the fuck did you find this hellhole?
你们怎么会找到这该死的矿坑的
Juno brought us here. She wanted us all to discover it.
朱诺带我们来的 她希望我们一起探索这里
She said she wanted to name it after me.
她还说想以我的名字命名这里
- Why? - Guilt.
- 为什么 - 因为她内疚
What happened between the two of you?
你俩之间到底发生了什么
My husband.
我丈夫
She had an affair with my husband.
她跟我丈夫有奸情
What happened to her?
那后来她怎么了
It was just Juno and me left.
当时只有我和朱诺逃脱了
Those things were coming for us,
那些怪物尾随而来
so I hurt her so I could get away.
所以我打伤了她自己逃命
She left my friend Beth dying.
她扔下我朋友贝丝一个人
Alone.
独自等死
When I found Beth, I had to put her out of her misery.
当我找到贝丝 不得不亲手结束她的痛苦
Save your torch.
手电省着点用
No, Juno, wait! Wait!
别 朱诺 等等
We came to get you out! Juno.
我们是来救你出去的 朱诺
Sarah brought us back down here. She brought us back.
是莎拉带我们来的 是她带我们回来救你的
Juno. Sarah is your friend.
朱诺 莎拉是你的朋友
- So you're the rescue party? - We're what's left.
- 救援队就你们三人吗 - 我们是幸存者
- Come on. We gotta get out of here. - Okay, listen to me.
- 快 我们得离开这 - 好的 听我说
Listen. Those things hunt above ground.
听着 这些怪物在陆面捕食
I think I know which way they go.
我想我知道他们从哪出去
They must have a route to the surface.
一定有一条路径是通向地面的
So, let's go.
好 我们出发吧
Wait a minute, so what? We go to where they feed?
等等 我们要去那些怪物觅食的地方吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
你开玩笑呢吧
Do you want to live? Silence is your best weapon.
你想活命吗 那就安静点
- Follow me. - We're following the water.
- 跟我走 - 我们要顺着水流走
I ain't going in no goddamn water. Juno knows the way out.
我可再也不下水了 朱诺知道出路
So how come you're still here?
你怎么会活下来的
Because my light died, I had no equipment,
因为我手电没电 也没有任何武器
and my climbing partner put
而且我的队友
a pick through my leg and ran out on me...
刺伤了我的腿跑掉了
There isn't time for this, God damn it!
现在不是谈论这事的时候 见鬼
We want to get out of here alive, we follow Juno.
如果想活着走出这里 我们就得让朱诺带路
No fucking way.
没门
God damn it! I brought
妈的 我带你
you into this hellhole, I'm taking you out.
进了这该死的矿坑 我就得带你活着出去
- Wait! - What? It's no good.
- 等等 - 怎么 这一点好处也没有
- Chief! - Shut up, Rios.
- 警长 - 里奥斯 你闭嘴
Let's move.
我们走
We'll have to go single file.
我们得一个一个过去
Spread your weight.
分摊体重
Keep it steady.
稳住
Easy, easy.
放松 放松
We really should do this one at a time.
我们真应该一个一个过去
You ran out on her, but you ain't running out on me,
你抛下她跑了 但你可别想抛下我
so let's get going.
所以我们要一起过
Shit!
妈的
- Help me! - Give me the bag.
- 帮帮我 - 把背包给我
Juno, help me, please! Juno!
朱诺 帮帮我 求你了
My arm! Pull me up!
抓住我手臂 拉我上去
Grab my pick.
取我的登山镐来
Okay. Okay.
好的 拿到了
- Cut. - What? Cut what?
- 切断 - 什么 切断什么
Cut it, or they'll both die!
切断它 不然我们都得死
Just fucking cut it!
快他妈切断它
- Do it now! - Wait! Wait!
- 快点 - 等等
Hurry!
快啊
Fuck. Okay.
妈的 好了
We gotta move.
我们得走了
We gotta go.
Rios.
里奥斯
Sarah.
莎拉
Let's go.
我们走
Come on. Come on!
趁现在快逃吧
- I can't... - No.
- 我不行了 - 不
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
- 对不起 - 都过去了
It's okay.
没关系
Sarah.
莎拉
Sarah, we can't stay here.
莎拉 此地不宜久留
Sarah. We have to get out of here now.
莎拉 我们现在得赶快离开这
Sarah.
莎拉
Please.
快啊
Come on.
拜托